Guide to the Charles Owen Rice Papers, 1894-2005 AIS.1976.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Subject Files, 1894-2005; I.
  - Vietnam
    - Crank Mail, 1965-1973 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Debate with Father Daniel Lyons, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Deserters' Amnesty Fund, 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - March on Washington, D.C., 1971 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Milwaukee Conference, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Anti-War Organizations, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous Anti-War Organizations, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous Anti-War Organizations, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous Anti-War Organizations, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings and Publications, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - National Mobilization Committee To End The War In Vietnam, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - New Mobilization Committee To End The War in Vietnam, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - New Mobilization Committee To End The War In Vietnam, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - New York Convention, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - News Clippings, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - News Clippings, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Ohio Valley Regional Coalition Committee, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Peace Torch March, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Pittsburgh Peach March, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Preparations for 1969 Washington, D.C. Demonstration, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Speaking Engagement for the Northeast Ohio Chapter of the Trade Union Division of SANE, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Spring Mobilization Committee, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - U.N. Peace March, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - VISTA, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Washington, D.C., Peace Rally, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Villanova University Honorary Doctorate, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Volvo, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Wagner Act, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Wall Street Journal Clippings, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Wanderer, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - War Objections, Catholics, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - War on Poverty, 1967-1983 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Washington Hospital, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Washington Industrial Development Corp., 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Washington Library, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Washington Youth Committee, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Watko, Maria, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Welch, John, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Welfare, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Werner, Kathy, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - West Pennsylvania Hospital Strike, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Western Electric Co., 1973 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Western Union Strike, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Western PA Committee of Independent Voters for Roosevelt and Wallace, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp., 1939-1941 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp., 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Westinghouse Federation of Salaried Employees, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Whittman and Pratt, Advertisers, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - WIIC-TV, Dave Kelly controversy, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Wilson, Desmon, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Witness Fee Scandal, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - WJAS Radio Station, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - WJAS Radio Station, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - WJAS Radio Station, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Women, Status of, 1960-1965 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Woodworkers Union, 1946-1948 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Works Progress Administration, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - World War II, 1941-1945 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Wright, Bishop John, Personal Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Wright, Bishop John, Personal Correspondence, 1959-1969 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Wright, Bishop John, Personal Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Wright, Bishop John, Personal Correspondence, 1967-1975 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - WWSW Radio Station, 1940-1959 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - WWSW Radio Station, 1940-1959 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - WWSW Radio Station, 1958-1960 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - WWSW Radio Station, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - WWSW Radio Station, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Yablonski, Jock, 1944-1947 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Young, Dr. William Lindsay, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Young Women's Christian Association, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Youth and Democracy Committee, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Zoning Controversy, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1932-2004; II.
  Series II consists of incoming and outgoing correspondence for the years 1932 through 2004. The correspondence is divided into two subseries. The first is arranged chronologically by year, and the second is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - By Year, 1.
    - 1932 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - 1933 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - 1934 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - 1935 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - 1936 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - 1937 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - 1938 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - 1939 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - 1940 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - 1941 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - 1942 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - 1943 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - 1944 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - 1945 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - 1946 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - 1947 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - 1948 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - 1949 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - 1950 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - 1951 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - 1952 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - 1953-1956 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - 1960 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - 1962 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - 1962 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - 1962 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - 1963 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - 1963 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - 1963 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - 1963 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - 1964 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - 1964 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - 1964 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - 1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - 1964 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - 1964 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - 1965 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - 1965 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - 1965 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - 1965 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - 1966 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - 1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - 1967 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - 1968 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - 1969 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - 1970 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - 1971 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - 1972 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - 1972 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - 1973 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - 1974 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - 1975 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - 1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - 1976 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - 1976 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - 1977 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - 1978 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - 1979 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - 1980 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - 1981 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - 1982 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - 1983 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - 1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - 1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - 1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - 1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - 1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - 1987 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - 1987 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - 1988 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - 1989 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - 1989 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - 1989 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - 1990 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - 1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - 1990 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - 1990 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - 1991 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - 1991 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - 1991 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - 1992 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - 1992 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - 1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - 1993 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - 1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - 1994 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - 1994 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - 1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - 1995 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - 1995 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - 1996 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - 1996 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - 1997 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - 1997 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - 1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - 1998 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - 1998 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - 1999 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - 1999 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - 1999 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - 1999 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - 2000 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - 2001 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - 2002 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - 2003 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - By Subject, 2.
    - Anderson, Robert L., 1996 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Angelo, Pat, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Bechteel, Earl, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Beuilacqua, Anthony J., 1983-1988 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1991-1993 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Burnley, Jack and Delores, 1992-1999 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Burnley, Jack and Delores, 1996-1999 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Butler, James G., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Catholic Bulletin, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Connelly, Carmel, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Conneely, M.J., 1992 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Cooke, Patrick, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Corconan, George J., 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Cort, John C., 1989 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Coyne, Pat, 1993, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Darke, Mary L., 2000 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Davies, Richard W., 1986 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Day, Art, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Dearden, John Francis, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Deedy, John, 1990-1997 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Diamond, Sigmund, 1982, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Dowds, John, 1986-1990 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Doyle, Margaret and Robert, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Fisher, James, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Flaherty, Peter, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Foerster, Tom, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Garvey, James W., 1989 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Gavaler, Campion, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Gibbons, Russell, 1992-1998 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Gilchrist, Cookie, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Ginder, Richard, 1979-1983 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Gustafson, Fred, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Hafer, Barbara, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Carolyn G., 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Higgins, George G., 1989-1992 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Higgins, George G., 1990-1997 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Leab, Daniel J., 1988-1999 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Lee, Donald J., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Mayer, David, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - McBride, Lloyd, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - McClung Lee, Alfred, 1980-1985 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Moore, Richard A., 1990 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - O'Donnell, L.A., 1983-1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Pitt, William L., 1991 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Quill, Shirley G., 1977-1992 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Radelet, John, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Rini, Suzanne, 1982-1986 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Rini, Suzanne, 1988-1990 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Rosswurm, Steve, 1985-1992 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Rush, Molly, 1988-1991 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Savoie, Edmund, 1994-1996 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Savoie, Edmund, 1995-1999 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Schatz, Ronald W., 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Seltzer, Robert Allen, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Shissler, Joanne, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Solovy, Jonathan S., 1982 (Box 29, Folder 21, Folder 20)
    - Starr, Jerry, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 22, Folder 21)
    - University of Pittsburgh, Archives of Industrial Society, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 23, Folder 22)
    - University of Pittsburgh, Special Collections, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 24, Folder 23)
    - Weaver, Clyde, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 24, Folder 25)
    - Woodrum, Myrtle Agnes, 1990-1994 (Box 29, Folder 25, Folder 26)
    - Wuerl, Donald, 1988-1998 (Box 29, Folder 26, Folder 27)
    - Addresses, undated (Box 29, Folder 27, Folder 28)
- Radio Broadcasts, 1937-1981; III.
  Series III contains notes, drafts, and outlines for Father Rice's radio show and other broadcasts of sermons and lectures. This series is divided into two subseries. The first is arranged chronologically by year, and the second is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - By Year, 1.
    - 1937 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - 1938 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - 1939 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - 1939 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - 1940 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - 1940 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - 1940 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - 1940 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - 1941 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - 1941 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - 1941 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - 1941 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - 1942 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - 1942 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 1942 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - 1942 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - 1943 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - 1943 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - 1943 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - 1943 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - 1944 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - 1944 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - 1944 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - 1944 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - 1945 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - 1945 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - 1945 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - 1945 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - 1946 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - 1946 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - 1946 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - 1946 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - 1947 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - 1947 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - 1947 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - 1947 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - 1948 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - 1948 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - 1948 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - 1948 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - 1949 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - 1949 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - 1949 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - 1949 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - 1950 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - 1950 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - 1950 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - 1950 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - 1951 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - 1951 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - 1951 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - 1951 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - 1952 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - 1952 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - 1952 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - 1952 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - 1953 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - 1953 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - 1953 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - 1953 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - 1954 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - 1954 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - 1954 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - 1954 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - 1955 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - 1955 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - 1955 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - 1955 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - 1956 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - 1956 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - 1956 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - 1956 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - 1957 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - 1957 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - 1957 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - 1957 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - 1958 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - 1958 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - 1958 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - 1958 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - 1959 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - 1959 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - 1959 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - 1959 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - 1960 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - 1960 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - 1960 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - 1960 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - 1961 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - 1961 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - 1961 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - 1961 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - 1962 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - 1962 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - 1962 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - 1962 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - 1963 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - 1963 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - 1963 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - 1963 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - 1964 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - 1964 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - 1964 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - 1964 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - 1965 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - 1965 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - 1965 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - 1965 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - 1966 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - 1966 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - 1966 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - 1966 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - 1967 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - 1967 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - 1967 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - 1968 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - 1967 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - 1968 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - 1968 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - 1968 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - 1969 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - 1969 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - 1969 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - By Subject, 2.
    - Christmas, 1975, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Christmas, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence Regarding Rice's Broadcasts on WWSW, 1970-1980 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence Regarding Rice's Broadcasts on WJAS, 1970-1973 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Labor and Social Encyclical, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Protest Against Nazi Brutalism, 1941-1942 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Television Broadcast, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Arbitration Cases, 1940-1965; IV.
  Series IV contains materials relating to arbitration cases that Father Rice was involved with including cases with Teamsters, Laundy Workers, and Steelworkers. This series is divided into two subseries. The first is arranged alphabetically by subject, and the second is arranged chronologically by year.
  - By Subject, 1.
    - Altoona Rayon Weaving Mill vs. Textile Workers Union of America, undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - American Coat, Apron and Towel Company vs. Laundry Workers Union, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - A P Tea Company vs. Retail Food Stores Union Local 590, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - A P Tea Company vs. Teamsters Union Local 249, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Arbitration Cases, Fees, undated (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Armstrong Cork Company vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum Plastic Workers of America, Local 255, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Armstrong Grocery Company of Sharon vs. Teamsters Union, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Black Hawk Press vs. International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, Local 73, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Braeburn Alloy Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, CIO Local, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Brighton Foundry Company vs. Gen. Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 249, AFL, no date (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Champion Laundry vs. Laundry Workers International Union, Local 141, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Duraloy Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2810, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Duquesne Light Company vs. Independent Association of Employees of Duquesne Light Co., Assoc. Companies, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Eagle Linen Supply vs. International Laundry Workers of America, AFL, Local 141, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Fort Duquesne Laundry vs. Int. Laundry Workers, AFL, Local 141, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Fort Pitt Bedding Company vs. United Furniture Workers CIO, Local 100, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Fort Pitt Bedding Company vs. United Furniture Workers CIO, Local 100, 1941-1942 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Fort Pitt Manufacturing Company vs. United Furniture Workers CIO, Local 100, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Fort Pitt Manufacturing Company vs. United Furniture Workers CIO, Local 100, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Fort Pitt Manufacturing Company vs. United Furniture Workers CIO, Local 100, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Fort Pitt Manufacturing Company vs. United Furniture Workers, CIO Local 100, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 40-48, Folder 40)
    - Fried Reineman Company vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers of North America, AFL, Local 424, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Gammon's vs. Hotel Restaurant Employees Alliance, Local 237, AFL, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Heppenstall Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1601, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Heppenstall Company vs. Un. Steelworkers of America, Local 1601, CIO, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Highland Laundry Company vs. International Laundry Workers of America, Local 141, AFL, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Highland Laundry Company vs. International Laundry Workers of America, Local 141, AFL, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Independent Towel Supply Company vs. Int'l Laundry Workers of America, Local 14, AFL, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Iron City Industrial Cleaning vs. Int'l Laundry Workers of America, Local 141, AFL, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - J. Kenny Transfer Company vs. Int'l Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen Helpers of America, Local 249, AFL, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Long Transportation Company vs. Int'l Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen Helpers of America, Local 249, AFL, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - May-Stern Company vs. Int'l Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen Helpers of America, Local 249, AFL, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Moore, Lee C. Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2372, CIO, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - National Malleable Steel Castings Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1477, CIO, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - North Laundry vs. Int'l Laundry Workers of America, Local 141, AFL, undated (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
    - North Laundry vs. Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Ware-housemen Helpers of America, Local 249, AFL, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - North Side Packing Co., vs. Amal. Meat Cutters Workmen of North America, Local 424, AFL, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Oswald Hess Company vs. Amal. Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 424, AFL, undated (Box 34, Folder 7-8)
    - Oswald Werner and Sons Company vs. Int'l Union of Cleaning and Dye House Workers, Local Union No. 9, AFL, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Overhold, A. Company vs. United Brewers, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drinks and Distillery Workers, Local 71, CIO, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Page Steel and Wire Div. American Chain Cable Co., Inc. vs. Steelworkers Organizing Committee, Lodge No. 1391, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Paulson Cleaning and Dye Company vs. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local 75, AFL, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Paulson Cleaning and Dye Company vs. International Brotherhood of House Workers, Local 9, AFL, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania Paper Stock Company of Pittsburgh vs. Int'l Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen Helpers, Local 609, AFL, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Penn Cash Markets, Inc. vs. Amal. Meat Cutters Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 424, AFL, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Penn Overall and Supply Company vs. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local 75, AFL, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Perfect Laundry vs. Int'l Laundry Workers of America, Local 141, AFL, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Perfect Laundry vs. Int'l Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen Helpers of America, AFL, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Pittsburgh Laundry vs. Int'l Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen Helpers of America, Local 249, AFL, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Pittsburgh Lumber Institute of Allegheny County vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1160, AFL, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Vulcan Iron Works, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - White Swan Laundry vs. Int'l Laundry Workers of America, Local 141, AFL, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - By Year, 2.
    - 1944, 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - 1953 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - 1956 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - 1957 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - 1959 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - 1960 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - 1961 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - 1962 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - 1963 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - 1964 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - 1965 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- FBI Files, 1947-1986; V.
  Series V contains materials relating to files kept by the FBI headquarters in Washington, D.C. and Pittsburgh field office on Father Rice and his activities, both in the labor and the civil rights movements. The series was split into two subseries in July 2011 with the addition of material obtained from researchers.
  - Files Obtained by Father Rice, 1.
    This subseries contains copies of files maintained by the FBI regarding Father Rice that were obtained through a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request in 1977. These files were kept in Father Rice's office and were arranged chronologically. Also present is correspondence between Father Rice and the FBI regarding his FOIA request.
    - Correlation Summary, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1986 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - File Documents, 1947, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - File Documents, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 4)